Miscellany
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Miscellany
2.1.2.4.21.3
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1392
- Miscellany, 2.1.2.4.21.3
  - The Old Pentateuch Roll, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x3 b&w (Box 1392)
  - Railroad station, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Large outdoor gathering of people, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x3 b&w (Box 1392)
  - Building façade, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x3 color (Box 1392)
  - Building facade, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x3 b&w (Box 1392)
  - Ornate interior of building, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Fern, circa 1900-1920; 37; 3x3 color (Box 1392)
  - Tree-lined staircase, circa 1900-1920; 38; 3x3 color (Box 1392)
  Box 1393
- Miscellany, 2.1.2.4.21.3
  - Man on tree-lined road, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x3 color (Box 1393)
  - Waterfall, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x3 color (Box 1393)
  - Landscape, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x3 color (Box 1393)
  - Landscape, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x3 color (Box 1393)
  - Axeustsane, Leyern, circa 1900-1920; 5; 23575; 3x4 color (Box 1393)
  - Place of worship[?], circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x3 b&w (Box 1393)
  - Landscape, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x3 color (Box 1393)
  - Landscape painting, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1393)
  - Statue, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1393)
  - Row of buildings with arched facades, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1393)
  - Family portrait, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1393)